<panel
  id="homepage"
  color="Black"
  >

  <Image
    image="titleimage"
  ></Image>

  <button
    color="#326273"
    shadow="#C4AF9A"
    shadowDistance="4 -6"
    position="0 -100 0"
    height="200"
    width="1000"
    textColor="White"
    fontSize="60"
    onClick="startGame"
    ></button>

  <image
    image="playGameText"
    height="175"
    width="800"
    position="0 -100 0"
    ></image>

  <button
    shadow="#38023B"
    color="#C4AF9A"
    shadowDistance="4 -6"
    position="-300 -350 0"
    height="100"
    width="400"
    textColor="White"
    fontSize="60"
    onClick="about"
    ></button>

  <image
    image="aboutText"
    height="75"
    width="300"
    position="-300 -350 0"
    ></image>

  <button
    shadow="#38023B"
    color="#C4AF9A"
    shadowDistance="4 -6"
    position="300 -350 0"
    height="100"
    width="400"
    textColor="White"
    fontSize="60"
    onClick = "showCredits"
    ></button>

  <image
    image="creditsText"
    height="75"
    width="300"
    position="300 -350 0"
    ></image>

  </panel>

<!-- Credits page -->
<panel
  id = "Credits"
  color = "Black"
  >

  <image
    image="ryanText"
    height="75"
    width="1000"
    position="0 100 0"
    >
  </image>
  <image
    image="devinText"
    height="75"
    width="1000"
    position="0 0 0"
    >
  </image>
  <image
    image="gabiText"
    height="75"
    width="1000"
    position="0 -100 0"
    >
  </image>

  <button
    color="#326273"
shadow="#C4AF9A"
shadowDistance="4 -6"
    width="200"
    height="200"
    position="0 -300 0"
    fontSize="40"
    textColor="White"
    onClick="onLoad"
    ></button>

  <image
    image="xText"
    height="180"
    width="180"
    position="0 -300 0"
    ></image>
</panel>

<!-- About page -->
<panel
  color = "Black"
  id="about"
  >

  <text
    color="White"
    fontSize="30"
    position="0 0 0"
    id="problemStatement"
    >Here at Team 2, we have learned the hard way that balancing nutrition, happiness, and money can be quite challenging as a college student.
    Because of this, we have created "Food for Thought" in the hopes that we can teach other students how to recognize unhealthy eating habits and correct them so
    they can properly balance nutrition, happiness, and money. While playing "Food for Thought," we hope that you learn the realities of modern day college
    students' eating habits by assuming the role of a college student and progressing through different meals. You will make decisions
    and end the day with three different scores, nutrition, happiness, and money. You start each day with $50, 0 happiness and 0 nutrition, by the
    end of the day the decisions you have made will effect your score. We hope it is obvious that the best score involves having a balanced
    nutrition, happiness, and money score.

    In the United States, the median age for young adults to move out and become independent is 19 years old. At this age, most of
    these young adults have just graduated high school and are moving out to attend college or begin a life in the workforce. These drastic
    changes in lifestyle, along with their newfound independence, can result in many unexpected things. The general problem is in the United
    States, these young adults are not meeting the 2020-2025 Dietary Guidelines for Americans (DGA) set forth by the USDA. The DGA state 1)
    follow a healthy eating pattern across the lifespan, 2) focus on variety, nutrient density, and amount, 3) limit calories from added
    sugars and saturated fats and reduce sodium intake, 4) shift to healthier food and beverage choices, and 5) support healthy eating
    patterns for all. Even with these guidelines, college students are often faced with a new reality; one in which they are attending
    school full time, working full/part-time, possibly doing extracurricular activities, and meeting up with friends, which limits the time of doing daily tasks
    like cooking and cleaning. This new reality can be very time-consuming and stressful, leading to poor dietary habits that are focused solely on money and time.

    The specific problem is that college students often lack the knowledge or understanding that preparing a healthy and delicious meal
    can be just as quick and inexpensive as the common student’s ramen dinner. The newly popular meal services like HelloFresh and MyPlate
    provide an easy way to show that a healthy, well-balanced meal can be made in less than 30 minutes and cost less than $2.49 a serving.
    By teaching college students how to budget for groceries, plan out meals to make grocery lists, shop for planned and unplanned groceries,
    and how to cook or meal prep with basic culinary skills, the number of college students that have the knowledge and experience to
    create well-balanced meals that that are both cheap and fit the DGA may increase. Hopefully "Food for Thought" teaches college students that
    well-balanced meals can be both cheap and quick, eliminating the need to consume cheap, overly-processed, and unhealthy foods.
  </text>

<button
    color="#326273"
shadow="#C4AF9A"
shadowDistance="4 -6"
    width="50"
    height="50"
    rectAlignment="UpperLeft"
    fontSize="40"
    textColor="White"
    onClick="onLoad"
    ></button>

  <image
    image="xText"
    height="40"
    width="40"
    rectAlignment="UpperLeft"
    offsetXY="5 -5"
    ></image>

</panel>

<!--Day 1 Morning Message Panel -->
<panel
  id="day1MMessage"
  color="Black"
  >
  <text
    color="White"
    fontSize="60"
    position="0 0 0"
    >You awake to the sound of your alarm. You groggily stir awake and get yourself ready for the day. You check your phone to see a text from
    your friends, asking if you want to meet up with them for breakfast. Reading that text you begin to realize that you’re hungry! You remember
    you went grocery shopping the other day and have all the ingredients to make your favorite breakfast food.</text>
</panel>

<!--Day 1 Morning Choice Panel -->
<panel
  id="day1MChoice"
  color="Black"
  >
  <text
    color="White"
    fontSize="80"
    position="0 200 0"
    >What will you do for breakfast?</text>

  <button
    color="#326273"
shadow="#C4AF9A"
shadowDistance="4 -6"
    position="-600 -100 0"
    height="200"
    width="400"
    textColor="White"
    fontSize="60"
    onClick="day1MOwn"
    ></button>

  <image
    image="bMake"
    height="1100"
    width="350"
    position="-600 -320 0"
    ></image>

  <button
    color="#326273"
shadow="#C4AF9A"
shadowDistance="4 -6"
    position="0 -100 0"
    height="200"
    width="400"
    textColor="White"
    fontSize="60"
    onClick="day1MOut"
    ></button>

  <image
    image="bMeet"
    height="1100"
    width="350"
    position="0 -120 0"
    ></image>

  <button
    color="#326273"
shadow="#C4AF9A"
shadowDistance="4 -6"
    position="600 -100 0"
    height="200"
    width="400"
    textColor="White"
    fontSize="60"
    onClick="day1MSkip"
    ></button>

  <image
    image="skipMeal"
    height="175"
    width="350"
    position="600 -100 0"
    ></image>
  </panel>

<!--Day 1 Morning Make Your Own Selected -->
<panel
  id="day1MOwn"
  color="Black"
  >
  <text
    color="White"
    fontSize="60"
    position="0 300 0"
    >You decide to save a little bit and make your own breakfast. You keep it simple by whipping up some eggs and toast. You eat it
    to the point where you are content. After finishing, a thought pops into your head.</text>

  <text
    id="day1MOwnPopUp"
    color="White"
    fontSize="80"
    position="0 100 0"
    >Do you want to pack a lunch for later today?</text>

  <button
    id="day1MOwnPopUpYesButton"
    color="#326273"
shadow="#C4AF9A"
shadowDistance="4 -6"
    position="-300 -100 0"
    height="200"
    width="400"
    textColor="White"
    fontSize="60"
    onClick="day1MOwnPopUpYes"
    >Yes</button>

  <button
    id="day1MOwnPopUpNoButton"
    color="#326273"
shadow="#C4AF9A"
shadowDistance="4 -6"
    position="300 -100 0"
    height="200"
    width="400"
    textColor="White"
    fontSize="60"
    onClick="day1MOwnPopUpNo"
    >No</button>
</panel>

<!--Day 1 Morning Go Out Selected Selected -->
<panel
  id="day1MOut"
  color="Black"
  >
  <text
    color="White"
    fontSize="60"
    position="0 200 0"
    >You just aren’t feeling like cooking at the moment. You run down to campus and meet up with your friends at the campus food court.
    But now you have so many options to choose from! What will you pick? But oh well!</text>
    <button
      id="day1MBreakfastBurrito"
      color="#326273"
  shadow="#C4AF9A"
  shadowDistance="4 -6"
      position="-600 -100 0"
      height="200"
      width="400"
      textColor="White"
      fontSize="60"
      onClick="day1MPickBurrito"
      ></button>
      <image
        image="burritoText"
        height="175"
        width="350"
        position="-600 -100 0"
        ></image>
      <button
        id="day1MCountrySteak"
        color="#326273"
    shadow="#C4AF9A"
    shadowDistance="4 -6"
        position="0 -100 0"
        height="200"
        width="400"
        textColor="White"
        fontSize="60"
        onClick="day1MPickSteak"
        ></button>
        <image
          image="steakText"
          height="175"
          width="350"
          position="0 -100 0"
          ></image>
        <button
          id="day1MFruitOatmeal"
          color="#326273"
      shadow="#C4AF9A"
      shadowDistance="4 -6"
          position="600 -100 0"
          height="200"
          width="400"
          textColor="White"
          fontSize="60"
          onClick="day1MPickFruitOatmeal"
          ></button>
          <image
            image="oatmealText"
            height="175"
            width="350"
            position="600 -100 0"
            ></image>

</panel>

<!--Day 1 Morning Got Burrito -->
<panel
  id="day1MBurrito"
  color="Black"
  >
  <text
    color="White"
    fontSize="60"
    position="0 0 0"
    >You decide to get something somewhat filling and get a breakfast burrito from one of the booths. It's pretty tasty! You talk with your friends for a while before heading to your classes.</text>
</panel>

<!--Day 1 Morning Got Steak -->
<panel
  id="day1MSteak"
  color="Black"
  >
  <text
    color="White"
    fontSize="60"
    position="0 0 0"
    >You decide that you deserve a treat, and get yourself some country fried steak from the nicer restaurant within the union. You get served a heaping plate of food that you savor every bite of. You talk with your friends while eating before heading to your classes.</text>
</panel>

<!--Day 1 Morning Got Oatmeal -->
<panel
  id="day1MFruit"
  color="Black"
  >
  <text
    color="White"
    fontSize="60"
    position="0 0 0"
    >Wanting to save a little bit of money and get something light, you get a small bowl of oatmeal and fruit. The fruit is fresh, and you can taste a bit of cinnamon in the oatmeal. You talk with your friends while eating and then head out to your classes.</text>
</panel>

<!--Day 1 Morning SkipSelected Selected -->
<panel
  id="day1MSkip"
  color="Black"
  >
  <text
    color="White"
    fontSize="60"
    position="0 0 0"
    >You shake the hunger away and decide that you really ought to get to class. Forgoing breakfast you run down to campus and get to your
    lecture with time to spare. However, you can’t shake the hunger gnawing at you and you're having trouble focusing in class.</text>
</panel>

<panel
  id="day1MInteraction"
  color="Black"
  >
  <Image
    image="kitchen"
    opacity="0.2"
  ></Image>

  <Image
    id="day1MInteractionPan"
    image="pan"
    height="150"
    width="800"
    position="75 -200 0"
  ></Image>
  <Image
    id="day1MInteractionEgg"
    image="egg"
    height="70"
    width="70"
    position="-100 100 0"
  ></Image>
  <Image
    id="day1MInteractionBrokenEgg"
    image="brokenegg"
    height="150"
    width="90"
    position="-100 100 0"
  ></Image>
  <Image
    id="day1MInteractionFriedEgg"
    image="friedegg"
    height="100"
    width="125"
    position="-100 -170 0"
  ></Image>
  <button
    id="day1MInteractionEggButton"
    height="200"
    width="200"
    opacity="0.0"
    color="#326273"
shadow="#C4AF9A"
shadowDistance="4 -6"
    position="-100 100 0"
    onClick="day1MInteractionBreakEgg"
    ></button>
  <button
    id="day1MInteractionPanButton"
    opacity="0.0"
    color="#326273"
shadow="#C4AF9A"
shadowDistance="4 -6"
    height="400"
    width="800"
    position="0 -200 0"
    onClick="day1MInteractionFlipEgg"
    ></button>
  <text
    id="day1MInteractionText"
    color="White"
    fontSize="80"
    position="0 400 0"
    >How To: Fry an Egg</text>

</panel>

<!--Day 1 Lunch Message Panel -->
<panel
  id="day1LMessage"
  color="Black"
  >
  <text
    color="White"
    fontSize="60"
    position="0 0 0"
    >You get through your first round of classes with little difficulty, leading to an hour of reprieve for you to do what you wish.
    Your mind drifts between different fun ideas of what to go and do, but before you can think too long you feel your stomach growl once again.
    </text>
</panel>

<!--Day 1 Lunch Choice Panel -->
<panel
  id="day1LChoice"
  color="Black"
  >
  <text
    color="White"
    fontSize="80"
    position="0 200 0"
    >What will you do for lunch?</text>

  <button
    color="#326273"
shadow="#C4AF9A"
shadowDistance="4 -6"
    position="-600 -100 0"
    height="200"
    width="400"
    textColor="White"
    fontSize="60"
    onClick="day1LFoodCourt"
    ></button>

    <image
      image="lMeet"
      height="175"
      width="350"
      position="-600 -100 0"
      ></image>

  <button
    color="#326273"
shadow="#C4AF9A"
shadowDistance="4 -6"
    position="0 -100 0"
    height="200"
    width="400"
    textColor="White"
    fontSize="50"
    onClick="day1LBackToDorm"
    ></button>

    <image
      image="lMake"
      height="1100"
      width="350"
      position="0 -100 0"
      ></image>

  <button
    color="#326273"
shadow="#C4AF9A"
shadowDistance="4 -6"
    position="600 -100 0"
    height="200"
    width="400"
    textColor="White"
    fontSize="60"
    onClick="day1LSkip"
    ></button>

  <image
    image="skipMeal"
    height="175"
    width="350"
    position="600 -100 0"
    ></image>

  </panel>

  <!--Day 1 Lunch made lunch -->
  <panel
    id="day1LMadeLunch"
    color="Black"
    >
    <text
      color="White"
      fontSize="60"
      position="0 0 0"
      >Good thing you packed a lunch! You find a quiet place outside and sit down to enjoy your meal.
      Opening your backpack, you pull out a sandwich and a bag of carrots. It only takes you a little time to finish your lunch and get on to enjoying your break!
      You run down to the library and play on the VR machines for the rest of the hour.
      Feeling happy and full you head to the rest of your classes</text>
  </panel>

  <!--Day 1 Lunch Food Court -->
  <panel
    id="day1LCourt"
    color="Black"
    >
    <text
      color="White"
      fontSize="60"
      position="0 150 0"
      >You decide to hit up the campus food court for some lunch. There are so many choices!
      What will you pick? </text>
      <button
        id="day1LPizza"
        color="#326273"
    shadow="#C4AF9A"
    shadowDistance="4 -6"
        position="-600 -100 0"
        height="200"
        width="400"
        textColor="White"
        fontSize="60"
        onClick="day1LPickPizza"
        ></button>
        <image
          image="pizzaText"
          height="175"
          width="350"
          position="-600 -100 0"
          ></image>
        <button
          id="day1LFoodTruck"
          color="#326273"
      shadow="#C4AF9A"
      shadowDistance="4 -6"
          position="0 -100 0"
          height="200"
          width="400"
          textColor="White"
          fontSize="60"
          onClick="day1LPickTruck"
          ></button>
          <image
            image="foodTruckText"
            height="175"
            width="350"
            position="0 -100 0"
            ></image>
          <button
            id="day1LSalad"
            color="#326273"
        shadow="#C4AF9A"
        shadowDistance="4 -6"
            position="600 -100 0"
            height="200"
            width="400"
            textColor="White"
            fontSize="60"
            onClick="day1LPickSalad"
            ></button>
            <image
              image="saladText"
              height="175"
              width="350"
              position="600 -100 0"
              ></image>

  </panel>

  <panel
    id="day1LPizzaText"
    color="Black"
    >
    <text
      color="White"
      fontSize="60"
      position="0 0 0"
      >Opting for something quick and easy, you jog over to the nearby pizza stand
    and get two slices of pepperoni pizza. They're greasy and served to you on a
  paper plate, but you like it! Feeling full and satisfied, you kill time for the
rest of your break on the VR machines before heading to your last bout of classes.</text>
  </panel>

  <panel
    id="day1LTruck"
    color="Black"
    >
    <text
      color="White"
      fontSize="60"
      position="0 0 0"
      >Wanting to treat yourself to a good lunch, you go to the sandwich melt Truck
    parked outside of the union. However, you're greeted a long line! Eventually
  you get to the front and get yourself a turkey bacon melt and a bag of chips to
go with it. However, between waiting in line, waiting for your food and then
finally eating it, you find that you've used up most of your break. Content with
your lunch but sad you didn't have more time, you head to your final bout of classes.</text>
  </panel>

  <panel
    id="day1LSaladText"
    color="Black"
    >
    <text
      color="White"
      fontSize="60"
      position="0 0 0"
      >Wanting to be healthy you head over to the salad bar, which was surprisingly
    busy! You get some romaine lettuce and top it off with your favorite toppings.
    the crisp lettuce really helps to refresh you, and you don't feel overly full
    or greasy. Happy with your choice you kill time for the rest of the hour before
    heading off to your final round of classes.</text>
  </panel>


  <!--Day 1 Lunch Back to Dorm -->
  <panel id="day1LDorm" color="Black" > <text color="White" fontSize="60"
  position="0 0 0" >Really not wanting to spend money, you decide to make the
  long walk back to your dorm and make yourself some lunch. You don't have much
  time to cook and you have a long walk back to campus so you decide on a
  something quick, filling, and on-the-go. A sandwich! The nice thing about
  sandwiches is the ability to swap out bread, meat, vegtables, and sauces so
  they are unique yet basic. You really enjoyed your egg this morning so you
  whip up another (this one a little more done so the yolk doesn't run), throw
  it on some bread with ham, avacado, spinach, tomato, cheese, and sriracha. It
  may not be the nicest looking meal but it has all the main food groups;
  grains, protein, vegetables, dairy, and to include fruit you pack an apple. It
  may not have been the most fun lunch and the walk was definelty long but your
  lunch cost $1.35, saving you somewhere between $9 and $16!!Full but a little
  irked, you make your way to the rest of your classes.</text> </panel>

  <!--Day 1 Lunch Skip -->
  <panel
    id="day1LSkipLunch"
    color="Black"
    >
    <text
      color="White"
      fontSize="60"
      position="0 0 0"
      >You look at the long lines, and the lack of your own food and decide that you’d rather go and do something fun instead.
       You head down to the library and use the VR setups, but the entire time you can’t shake the hunger gripping you.
       Disgruntled by your lack of planning, you head to your last few classes.</text>
  </panel>

  <!--Day 1 Dinner Message Panel -->
  <panel
    id="day1DinnerMessage"
    color="Black"
    >
    <text
      color="White"
      fontSize="60"
      position="0 0 0"
      >You come back to your dorm, tired after the long day of lectures.
      You sit down on your couch only to once again feel the familiar groan of your stomach.
      You look in your fridge and see groceries that you could throw together! Or you could order something in? Or go out?</text>
  </panel>

  <!--Day 1 Dinner Choice Panel -->
<panel
  id="day1DinnerChoice"
  color="Black"
  >
  <text
    color="White"
    fontSize="80"
    position="0 200 0"
    >What will you do for dinner?</text>

  <button
    color="#326273"
shadow="#C4AF9A"
shadowDistance="4 -6"
    position="-600 -100 0"
    height="200"
    width="400"
    textColor="White"
    fontSize="60"
    onClick="day1DMake"
    ></button>

  <image
    image="dMake"
    height="175"
    width="350"
    position="-600 -100 0"
    ></image>

  <button
    color="#326273"
shadow="#C4AF9A"
shadowDistance="4 -6"
    position="0 -100 0"
    height="200"
    width="400"
    textColor="White"
    fontSize="50"
    onClick="day1DOrder"
    ></button>

  <image
    image="dMeet"
    height="175"
    width="350"
    position="0 -100 0"
    ></image>

  <button
    color="#326273"
shadow="#C4AF9A"
shadowDistance="4 -6"
    position="600 -100 0"
    height="200"
    width="400"
    textColor="White"
    fontSize="60"
    onClick="day1DSkip"
    ></button>

  <image
    image="skipMeal"
    height="175"
    width="350"
    position="600 -100 0"
    ></image>
  </panel>

  <!--Day 1 Make Dinner-->
  <panel
    id="day1DMakeDinner"
    color="Black"
    >
    <Image
      image="kitchen"
      opacity="0.2"
    ></Image>
    <Image
      id="day1DInteractionPan"
      image="pan"
      height="150"
      width="800"
      position="75 -300 0"
    ></Image>
    <image
      id="day1Dseason1"
      image="salt"
      height="100"
      width="70"
      position="-100 100 0"
      ></image>
    <image
      id="day1Dseason2"
      image="pepper"
      height="100"
      width="70"
      position="-200 100 0"
      ></image>
    <image
      id="day1Dseason3"
      image="ceyenne"
      height="100"
      width="70"
      position="0 100 0"
      ></image>
    <image
      id="day1Draw"
      image="rawchicken"
      height="100"
      width="200"
      position="-100 -75 0"
      ></image>
    <image
      id="day1Dseasoned"
      image="seasonedchicken"
      height="100"
      width="200"
      position="-100 -75 0"
      ></image>
    <image
      id="day1Dcooked"
      image="cookedchicken"
      height="100"
      width="200"
      position="-100 -250 0"
      ></image>

    <button
      id="day1DSeasonButton"
      height="200"
      width="300"
      opacity="0.0"
      color="#326273"
shadow="#C4AF9A"
shadowDistance="4 -6"
      position="-100 100 0"
      onClick="day1DSeasonChicken"
      ></button>

    <text
      id="day1DInteractionText"
      color="White"
      fontSize="60"
      position="0 400 0"
      >You decide to cook yourself up some dinner.
     </text>
  </panel>

  <!--Day 1 Order Dinner-->
  <panel
    id="day1DOrderDinner"
    color="Black"
    >
    <text
      color="White"
      fontSize="60"
      position="0 200 0"
      >You feel too exhausted to cook, and decide instead to order dinner from Ubereats.
      What do you feel like ordering?
     </text>
     <button
       id="day1DBurger"
       color="#326273"
   shadow="#C4AF9A"
   shadowDistance="4 -6"
       position="-600 -100 0"
       height="200"
       width="400"
       textColor="White"
       fontSize="60"
       onClick="Day1DPickBurger"
       ></button>
       <image
         image="burgerText"
         height="175"
         width="350"
         position="-600 -100 0"
         ></image>
       <button
         id="day1DPasta"
         color="#326273"
     shadow="#C4AF9A"
     shadowDistance="4 -6"
         position="0 -100 0"
         height="200"
         width="400"
         textColor="White"
         fontSize="60"
         onClick="Day1DPickPasta"
         ></button>
         <image
           image="pastaText"
           height="175"
           width="350"
           position="0 -100 0"
           ></image>
         <button
           id="day1DSalad"
           color="#326273"
       shadow="#C4AF9A"
       shadowDistance="4 -6"
           position="600 -100 0"
           height="200"
           width="400"
           textColor="White"
           fontSize="60"
           onClick="Day1DPickSalad"
           ></button>
           <image
             image="saladText"
             height="175"
             width="350"
             position="600 -100 0"
             ></image>
  </panel>

  <panel
    id="day1DBurgerText"
    color="Black"
    >
    <text
      color="White"
      fontSize="60"
      position="0 0 0"
      >You're kind of craving a burger, so you decide to order one from one of the local
      joints. You wait a good 30 minutes for it to arrive, and find that the top bun slid
      off when the driver must have been turning. You piece it back together and enjoy your
      dinner while watching a show on Netflix. Full and content, you head to bed for the night.
     </text>
  </panel>

  <panel
    id="day1DPastaText"
    color="Black"
    >
    <text
      color="White"
      fontSize="60"
      position="0 0 0"
      >You decide that pasta sounds good, so you get some chicken and pasta from
      a local Italian restaurant. You wait a good 40 minutes for it to arrive. And when it
      does you've found that it's gotten a little cold. You reheat your dinner and then watch a
      show for the rest of the evening before heading to bed.
     </text>
  </panel>

  <panel
    id="day1DSaladText"
    color="Black"
    >
    <text
      color="White"
      fontSize="60"
      position="0 0 0"
      >Craving some Mexican Salad, you order some from the local mexican restaurant. You wait
      about 30 minutes for it to arrive, but it was worth the wait. The salad got a little soggy from
      the dressing, but that's alright. You enjoy your salad and watch a show before heading to bed for the evening.
     </text>
  </panel>


  <!--Day 1 Order Dinner-->
  <panel
    id="day1DSkipDinner"
    color="Black"
    >
    <text
      color="White"
      fontSize="60"
      position="0 0 0"
      >Tired from the day, you decide to just cut dinner and relax.
       You sit down on your couch and pull up Netflix on your TV. You browse the titles, too hungry to really make a decision.
       After a while you just call it quits and go to bed for the evening.
     </text>
  </panel>

<!--Day 1 End Panel -->
<panel
  id="day1End"
  color="Black"
  >
  <VerticalLayout>
  <text
    color="White"
    fontSize="60"
    position="0 0 0"
    >Congratulations! You made it through the end of the first day. We here at Team 2 sincerely hope that you enjoyed the experience.
  </text>
  <text
       id="Happiness Score"
       color="White"
       fontSize="60"
       position="0 0 0"
       >Your happiness score was:
  </text>
  <text
       color="White"
       fontSize="30"
       position="0 0 0"
       >You started the day at 0
  </text>
  <text
       id="Nutrition Score"
       color="White"
       fontSize="60"
       position="0 0 0"
       >Your nutrition score was:
  </text>
  <text
       color="White"
       fontSize="30"
       position="0 0 0"
       >You started the day at 0 for everything. Your days have carbs around 45-65%, protein 10-30%, and fat 20-35% and you should have between 1,600 and 3,000 calories per day depending on height, weight, and activity level.
  </text>
  <text
       id="Money Score"
       color="White"
       fontSize="60"
       position="0 0 0"
       >Your remaining money was: $
  </text>
  <text
       color="White"
       fontSize="30"
       position="0 0 0"
       >You started the day at $50
  </text>
  <HorizontalLayout>
    <button
      color="#326273"
shadow="#C4AF9A"
shadowDistance="4 -6"
      position="0 -100 0"
      height="200"
      width="200"
      textColor="White"
      fontSize="50"
      onClick="onLoad"
      ></button>

    <button
      color="#326273"
shadow="#C4AF9A"
shadowDistance="4 -6"
      position="0 -100 0"
      height="200"
      width="200"
      textColor="White"
      fontSize="50"
      onClick="optionsOutcomes"
      ></button>
    </HorizontalLayout>
  </VerticalLayout>
  <image
    image="playAgainButtonText"
    height="50"
    width="700"
    rectAlignment="lowerLeft"
    offsetXY="50 10"
    ></image>
  <image
    image="optionsButtonText"
    height="50"
    width="700"
    rectAlignment="lowerRight"
    offsetXY="-50 10"
    ></image>
</panel>

<panel
  id="optionsOutcomes"
  color="Black"
>
  <VerticalLayout>
    <text
         id="mainText"
         color="White"
         fontSize="60"
         position="0 0 0"
         >For each meal you had the option to..
    </text>
    <text
         id="topText"
         color="White"
         fontSize="60"
         position="0 0 0"
         >Cook
    </text>
    <text
         id="middleText"
         color="White"
         fontSize="60"
         position="0 0 0"
         >Eat out
    </text>
    <text
         id="bottomText"
         color="White"
         fontSize="60"
         position="0 0 0"
         >Skip Meal
    </text>
  </VerticalLayout>
</panel>

<button
  id="home"
  color="#326273"
  shadow="#C4AF9A"
  shadowDistance="4 -4"
  width="50"
  height="50"
  rectAlignment="UpperLeft"
  fontSize="40"
  textColor="White"
  onClick="onLoad"
  ></button>

<image
  id="home2"
  image="xText"
  height="40"
  width="40"
  rectAlignment="UpperLeft"
  offsetXY="5 -5"
  ></image>
